{
    "id": "2d5689d476654f2386a7c804366e2fb3",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There I met a very beautiful woman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "very",
                "beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The kind hostess made sure that everyone was happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sure",
                "everyone",
                "happy"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was wearing a red shirt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "red",
                "shirt"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich woman is known for her generosity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rich",
                "known",
                "generosity"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of being rich and famous, she leads a miserable life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "famous",
                "rich"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Her arrogant nature made her very unpopular.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrogant",
                "nature",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He wants to be a successful lawyer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "successful",
                "lawyer"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The anxious mother waited for a call from her son.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anxious",
                "mother",
                "call"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man has seen better days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "man",
                "days"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Iron is a useful metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "iron",
                "useful",
                "metal"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The offer was so good that I could not refuse it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "offer",
                "so",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}